arirang.com 2019-12-24

# The World On Arirang

## Privacy Policy for Members of Arirang’s Web Site

All personal information that The Korea International Broadcasting Foundation(hereinafter referred to as “Foundation”) handles is collected, retained, and processed under relevant statutes or with consent of each person whose information becomes subject to this Policy.

The Foundation's privacy policy takes effect on November 10, 2017.

The Personal Information Protection Act provides for general norms concerning managing personal information, and the Foundation will lawfully and properly manage the information collected, retained, and processed under the provisions of such statutes, so as to properly perform public services and appropriately protect citizens’ rights and interests.  
Futhermore, we, at The Korea International Broadcasting Foundation, respect your rights, including the right to request us to permit you to inspect your personal information retained by us and the right to request us to correct such information. You also have a right to file a petition for an administrative hearing to seek remedies for a violation of any of such rights under the Administrative Appeals Act. 

#### Article1 Purposes of Handling Personal Information

  * Your personal information processed by the Foundation are not used for any purpose other than the purposes specified in the following, and we will take necessary measures when any change occurs in the purposes of use, such as obtaining additional consent in accordance with Article 18 of the Personal Information Protection Act. 
    * Visitor management  
The Foundation manages the Personal information of visitors for identification, notification of complaints confirmation, and its results.
    * Managing recruitment and resourcing activities  
The Foundation will collect, use, store and otherwise process your Personal Data for the purposes of the Foundation’s recruitment or resourcing activities
  * The Foundation registers and discloses following Personal information according to Article 32 on the Protection of Personal information  No. | Name of personal  
information file | Consent to Use | Purpose of Handling | Website  
---|---|---|---|---  
1 | The list of field trip participants | Consent of a user whose information becomes subject to this Policy | Identification |   
2 | Managing recruitment and resourcing activities | Consent of a user whose information becomes subject to this Policy | to provide you with information relating to your application | [http://arirang.recruiter.co.kr](https://arirang.recruiter.co.kr/)  

#### Article2 Period during which Personal Information is Handled and Retained

  * The Foundation handles and retains personal information only during the period specified by relevant statutes for retaining and using personal information or the period to which each user consents when we collect the user’s personal information. 
  * The period during which a user’s personal information is handled and retained is as follows:  No. | Name of personal  
information file | Consent to Use | Period  
---|---|---|---  
1 | The list of field trip participants | Consent of a user whose information becomes subject to this Policy | 3 years  
2 | Managing recruitment and resourcing activities | Consent of a user whose information becomes subject to this Policy | 30 days after the end of recruitment process  

#### Article3 Matters concerning Provision of Personal Information to Third Parties

  * The Foundation does not provide personal information collected and retained thereby, to any third party without the relevant user’s consent, except in the following cases: 
    * Where a user specifically consents to provision of his/her personal information;
    * Where other statute provides expressly;
    * Where a user or his/her legal representative is incapable of communicating his/her intention or it is impossible to obtain consent from a user or his/her legal representative because his/her whereabouts are unknown but it is considered clearly necessary to urgently provide his/her personal information to a third party for the safety, health, or economic interests of the user or of a third party;
    * Where personal information is provided in a form that makes it impossible to identify a specific person, as necessary for compiling statistics or scientific research;
    * Where it is impracticable to perform relevant duties prescribed in other Acts unless personal information is provided for any purpose other than its original purpose or is provided to a third party and where such case is deliberated on and determined by the Personal Information Protection Commission;
    * Where it is necessary to provide such information to a foreign government or an international organization to implement treaties or other international agreements;
    * Where it is necessary to investigate a crime and to file and sustain a prosecution;
    * Where it is necessary for a court to proceed with a trial;
    * Where it is necessary to enforce a sentence, custody, or protective order imposed.
  * When we provide your personal information to a third party, we will inform you of the following facts to obtain consent from you: 
    * The name of the recipient of personal information (or the name of the corporation or organization, if the recipient is a corporation or organization) and the contact information of the recipient;
    * The recipient’s purposes of using personal information
    * The items of personal information to be provided.
    * The duration during which the personal information will be retained and used by the recipient.
    * The fact that the user has a right to refuse to consent and details of any disadvantages.

#### Article4 Matters concerning Outsourced Processing of Personal Information

  * The Foundation does not export its personal data without the data subject's consent outside the Foundation. If a third party organisation is contracted to process personal information on the Foundation’s behalf, the Foundation, as Data Controller, remains responsible for posting the name of company outsourced and outsourced matters on our website.
  * In accordance with Article 32 of the Personal Information Protection Act, the Foundation outsources the processing of a user’s personal information to maintain its website as follows:  No. | Company Outsourced | Outsourced Matters | Outsourcing Period | Tel.  
---|---|---|---|---  
1 | MIDAS IT | Recruitment website, Management of Recruitment Process, Managing Computer System Management, Customer Servvice | 30 days after recruitment process and expiration of outsourcing contract  | 031-789-0412  

#### Article5 The rights and obligations of data subjects and legal representatives, and how to exercise the rights

  * A user (if the user is under the age of 14, referring to his/her legal representative) may exercise the following rights in relation to protecting personal information: 
    * The right to request permission to inspect his/her personal information;
    * The right to request correction of his/her personal information if there is any error, etc.;
    * The right to request the deletion of his/her personal information;
    * The right to request the Foundation to suspend handling his/her personal information.
    * The right to be notified of personal information that has been received from another person
  * A user may exercise his/her rights prescribed in paragraph (1) by completing the form specified in attached Form 8 and submitting it to the Foundation by post, email or fax. The Foundation will take necessary measures promptly.  
[[Attached Form 8 of the Enforcement Rule of the Personal Information Protection Act] A request to [inspect, correct/delete, suspend handling] personal information](https://web.archive.org/web/20191224195805id_/http%3A//www.arirang.com/mobile/file/\[%EB%B3%84%EC%A7%801\]%EA%B0%9C%EC%9D%B8%EC%A0%95%EB%B3%B4_%EC%97%B4%EB%9E%8C%EC%A0%95%EC%A0%95%EC%82%AD%EC%A0%9C%EB%93%B1_%EC%9A%94%EA%B5%AC%EC%84%9C.hwp)
  * Where a user requests the correction or deletion of any error, etc., in his/her personal information, the relevant information shall not be provided to any third party pursuant to this Policy, until the relevant information is corrected or deleted.
  * A user may exercise his/her rights through an agent such as his/her legal representative or a person with a mandate. In such cases, the user shall submit a power of attorney as specified in attached Form 11 of the Enforcement Rule of the Personal Information Protection Act.  
[[attached Form 11 of the Enforcement Rule of the Personal Information Protection Act] Power of Attorney](https://web.archive.org/web/20191224195805id_/http%3A//www.arirang.com/mobile/file/\[%EB%B3%84%EC%A7%802\]%EA%B0%9C%EC%9D%B8%EC%A0%95%EB%B3%B4_%EC%97%B4%EB%9E%8C_%EC%A0%95%EC%A0%95%EC%82%AD%EC%A0%9C_%EC%9C%84%EC%9E%84%EC%9E%A5.hwp)
  * Users must not infringe on their own privacy or the privacy of other people collected by the Foundation by violating the Act on the Protection of Personal Information.

#### Article6 Items of Personal Information to be Handled

  * The main personal information collected and retained by the Foundation, are as follows;  No. | Name of personal information file | Main Items  
---|---|---  
1 | The list of field trip participants | Name, Contact Information, E-mail, Affiliation  
2 | Managing recruitment and resourcing activities | Name, Nationality, Address, Phone number, Hobby, Strength, Essay, Veterans’ Family, Disability Identification, Telephone number, Educational data, GPA, Military Service, Employment History, Travel Information, experience of studying abroad, Activities, English Proficiency or other language, Certificates, Awards ect.  

#### Article7 Destruction of Personal Information 

  * In principle, the Foundation destroys a user’s personal information after the period during which the personal information is retained ends or the purposes of handling the personal information have been attained. 
  * If the Foundation needs to retain the provided information in line with the relevant laws even when the agreed retention period is over or after achieving the purpose of its collection, it shall move the personal information in question (or personal information file) to a separate database or another storage space.
  * The procedure, deadlines, and methods for destroying it are as follows: 
    * Procedure for destruction   
The Foundation destroys personal information (or personal information files) according to a special procedure. The Foundation selects personal information (or personal information file) subject to destruction, obtains approval from the person in charge of personal information protection, and destroys it.
    * Methods for destruction   
The Foundation destroys personal information stored in the form of electronic files using the Low Level Format, which cannot be revived. Personal information stored in the form of paper documents is destroyed by shredding or incineration.

#### Article8 Cookie Policy

  * Purpose of Cookies 
    * The Foundation use cookies to give you the best experience on our website. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. 
    * These cookies enable the Foundation to anonymously track how visitors access and browse our website, thereby enabling us to optimise and improve our service.
    * The Foundation can use cookies to identify the user or device and to collect information.
  * Cookie Management 
    * Most internet browsers are initially set up to automatically accept cookies. You can change the settings to block cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent to your device.   

      * ☞ To view or modify cookies settings, follow these steps:
      * (1) In Internet Explorer, click Internet Options on the Tools menu, and then click the Security tab.
      * (2) Click the Web content zone you want, and then click Custom Level.
      * (3) Under Cookies, click the options you want, click OK, and then click OK.
    * If you disable the cookies that we use, this may impact your experience while on the Foundation Sites, for example you may not receive personalised service we provide on our website.

#### Article9 Measures for Ensuring Safety of Personal Information

  * The Foundation has taken the following technical and physical measures necessary for ensuring safety, in compliance with Article 29 of the Personal Information Protection Act: 
    * Handling measures : Formulating and implementing internal management plans and educating employees (personnel authorized to handle personal information )
    * Technical measures : Control of access to the personal information processing system, installation of access control systems, encryption of passwords, and installation of security programs
    * Physical measures : Restricting access by unauthorized persons

#### Article10 Remedies for Violation of Rights and Interests

  * Users can file complaints when their privacy has been infringed. 
    * Complaints regarding privacy violations 
      * Department: Management Support Team
      * Person in charge: Bang Seok-chul
      * Phone: 02-3475-5262, E-mail: privacy@arirang.com, Fax: 02-3475-5059
  * Users can request help from the following organizations in case they are not satisfied with the way the Foundation addressed their complaints. 
    * Higher organization (Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism) 
      * Responsibilities: Reports of privacy violations, consultations
      * Website : [http://www.mcst.go.kr](http://www.mcst.go.kr/)
      * Tel. : 044-203-2269
      * Address : Bldg. 15, Sejong Government Complex, 388 Galmae-ro, Sejong 30119 Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, Sejong Government Complex 
    * Personal Information Infringement Report Center (Korea Internet and Security Agency) 
      * Responsibilities: Reports of privacy violations, consultations
      * Website : [http://privacy.kisa.or.kr](http://privacy.kisa.or.kr/)
      * Tel. : 118
      * Address : Privacy Violation Report Center, Korea Internet & Security Agency, 135 Jungdae-ro, Songpa-gu, Seoul 138-950
    * The Personal Information Dispute Mediation Committee (Korea Internet and Security Agency) 
      * Responsibilities: Personal information disputes arbitration, collective dispute arbitration (civil arbitration)
      * Website : [http://www.kopico.go.kr](http://www.kopico.go.kr/)
      * Tel. : 1833-6972
      * Address : Privacy Violation Report Center, Korea Internet & Security Agency, 135 Jungdae-ro, Songpa-gu, Seoul 138-950
    * The Cyber Crime Investigation Team of the Supreme Prosecutors’ Office: (Tel.)1301, (E-mail) cid@spo.go.kr ([http://www.spo.go.kr](http://www.spo.go.kr/))
    * he Cyber Terrorism Response Center of the National Police Agency: (Tel.)182 ([http://cyberbureau.police.go.kr](http://cyberbureau.police.go.kr/))
  * Any person whose rights or interests are violated by any disposition or inaction of the head of a public agency with regard to a request made under the provisions of Article 35, 36, or 37 of the Personal Information Dispute Mediation Committee, may file a petition for an administrative hearing in accordance with the provisions of the Administrative Appeals Act. 
  * ※ For more information on administrative trials, visit the Website of the Administrative Appeals Commission ([http://www.simpan.go.kr](http://www.simpan.go.kr/))

#### Article11 Requests to Inspect Personal Information

  * A user may request the Foundation to permit him/her to inspect his/her personal information under Article 35 of the Personal Information Protection Act. The Foundation will strive to ensure that such request will be processed without delay. 
    * Department in charge of personal information viewing 
      * Department: Management Support Team
      * Name: Bang Seok-chul
      * Tel. : 02-3475-5262, E-mail : [scbang@arirang.com](mailto:scbang@arirang.com), fax) 02-3475-5059
  * Users can also view their personal information by visiting the Ministry of Interior’s personal information protection portal (www.privacy.go.kr)([http://www.privacy.go.kr](http://www.privacy.go.kr/)) 
    * inistry of Interior personal information protection portal ([http://www.privacy.go.kr](http://www.privacy.go.kr/)) → Personal Information Services → View Personal Information (authorization required)

#### Article12 Managers and Officers in Charge of Managing Personal Information 

  * In order to ensure the legality of personal information and the appropriateness of procedures to protect citizens’ rights and interests, and to properly perform public services, the Foundation appoints one of its personnel as the officer in charge of protecting personal information as follows: For any question or inquiry about personal information retained by the Foundation and the policy on the protection of personal information, please do not hesitate to contact us by any of the following means 
    * Information Protection Officer  Category  | Position | Name | Contact Information  
---|---|---|---  
Personal information protection superintendent | Management Support Team, Deputy Director | Choi Seong-Bae | Tel. 02-3475-5041  
Personal information manager | Management Support Team, Deputy Chief | Bang Seok-chul | Tel. 02-3475-5262Email  
Fax 02-3475-5059  

  * Users can inquire the staff in charge of personal information protection about any matters, complaints and disputes related to personal information that they have submitted to use the Foundation’s services. The Foundation shall respond to users’ inquiries without delay.

#### Article 13 Modified Personal Information Collection Agreement

The modified personal information collection agreement takes effect on November 10, 2017  
Please find the previous versions of Personal Information Collection Agreement below.
